What if I told you I tried to make a
million dollars in under 6 hours trading
and I almost made it? Well, if you
weren't part of it live or you didn't
[music] see the before I entered the
position, you probably wouldn't believe
it. Well, that's why exactly I recorded
everything live, shared it on my
Instagram, shared it on my TikTok, on my
community in Telegram and tens of
thousands of people, literally tens of
thousands people as you can see here,
caught the exact same position that I
shared hours before it happened. FOMC
was coming up a couple hours before I
entered these positions and I explained
to people the reasoning as to why it
should have a high probability of going
to the downside. So, let me give you the
context on how I actually almost made a
million dollars. Now, first of all, you
guys may probably wondering how can I
possibly make a million dollars on a
single trade? Am I taking a hun- a
single hundred dollars into a million
dollars? Am I risking a million dollars
to make another million dollars? No. So,
I have a three million dollar trading
account with this specific account that
I took these trades on and I decided to
risk about a hundred and thirty, hundred
and forty thousand dollars per position.
So, I'm basically risking three hundred
thousand dollars on this one specific
trade. And if I were to catch a one to
four risk to reward after fees, after
swap, I would be left with a million
dollars. So, I'm putting up at risk
three hundred thousand dollars in order
so I can make a million dollars. Now, I
quite did not get there. I ended up
closing at seven hundred thousand
dollars and I want to give you the full
picture as to why I did that and why I
decided to not hold the entire way. And
where if I would have held, the trade
would have actually reached my million
dollar take profit. So, let me give you
the full context and breakdown behind
this trade that still has so much more
potential to continue in the direction
that I predicted. So, the two markets
that I identified on Sunday that I was
extremely interested in entering the
position was going to be NZD USD and EUR
USD. Now, both of these positions have
already had the big move to the
downside. It almost looks quite obvious
that this move was predictable at this
area after the fact that it happened.
But, I need you to understand the real
reasoning as to why I entered this
position. So, let's take this back 48
hours prior to this having to move. So,
when I did my Sunday swings with my
students, which I break down the top
markets that I'm interested in trading
with them every single Sunday live, the
first thing that I identified on NZD/USD
is my top-down analysis. I identified
the weekly time frame being extremely
bearish. Now, many people would claim
that it could be bearish from this lower
high to this lower low, and they would
be very very incorrect because the
correct lower high would be this lower
high and [music] this lower low. Now,
while it doesn't really change much in
this move, it would actually lead you to
determining that you can have a very
clean weekly area of interest right here
in the middle. Whenever we're below, we
have very strong rejections to the
downside. Whenever we're above, we head
up. Whenever we're below, we head down.
We head down. Whenever we're above, we'd
head up. So, the week 2 weeks prior to
where we are right now,
we had a massive weekly bearish
engulfing candlestick closing below that
area. The week prior to that, we came
back and then retested. So, not only
does this indicate to me that we're
below this area, when I go to the daily
time frame, I can see a very strong head
and shoulders pattern, which is my
favorite reversal pattern that exists in
the market. So, you can have here left.
You can have this be a head and then
this be a a weird right shoulder, bit
unproportionate. But, the most impactful
reasoning that I entered this position
is because of the daily time frame. It's
the market placement and where this
market is at this specific area. As you
can see, this is a very well-respected
daily support area. Whenever we're
above, we head up. Whenever we're below,
we head down. It really is that simple.
Many people, they get confused when
should I trade with the trend? Should I
trade off of areas of interest and
support and resistance? When you become
an experienced trader,
you understand that market placement is
much more important for entering a
position and the trend is your friend to
[music] that let you determine into
where you should hold your take profit.
But, where you enter a position is not
purely off of the trend. The trend will
only tell you that you should just go in
that direction. Now, where your entry is
in that direction is where this area of
interest comes in and is extremely key.
So, this area of interest, not only have
we broken below it, we've retested it,
we've rejected it, we've came up have
had this massive liquidity grab, which
is this is the fake out, this is the the
institutions taking out the retail
traders fake out, wick out, whatever you
want to call it. And after that, we
still managed to close to the downside.
So, not only does this look beautiful
that we're still below it, but we
already saved ourselves from entering at
this area of interest because the wick
out has already happened. And I can tell
the wick out has already happened
because when I go down to the 4-hour,
what I see is a perfect head and
shoulders pattern that is forming on
itself. And if I just look left, I can
very much see that this market is built
off of head and shoulder pattern. Left
head, right shoulder here.
We have another bigger head and
shoulders pattern right here. Left head
and then a right shoulder right here. We
have another head and shoulders patterns
right here. Left head, right shoulder
and then obviously the one that we were
forming right here. We have a left head
and then a right shoulder that we were
about to form. So, I'm really just
looking left
for me to be able to guess what's going
to happen to the right. And if every
single time something happens exactly
like what happened previously, I can
expect for it to happen again. So, this
market has had the liquidity grab, which
is this fake out right here. We broke
the structure because this market was
bearish. Lower low, lower high, lower
low, higher high, higher low, higher
high. We shifted the structure making
this market bearish and then we came
back to retest this area once again.
This is exactly where I was looking for
my entry signal on this position to head
to the downside. We're right at the
smack middle of the week. We are prior
to a very volatile session which is
London session and all I'm waiting for
is my perfect engulfing candlestick to
enter. Now, I get my engulfing
candlestick but as soon as I get that
engulfing candlestick, I'm not active in
front of the markets. I don't remember
really what I was doing but I wasn't
active. And then I simply come back into
the market a couple of hours later and I
see that it has indeed rejected from
this right shoulder.
I would much rather enter a position off
of a confirmation rather than
anticipation. I'd rather enter the
position later into the trade after the
market has shown me its hand first
instead of me anticipating that this is
going to be a right shoulder and I try
and get a sniper entry all the way at
the top here. I see many traders get
burned [music] trying to predict these
perfect sniper entries and it really
doesn't make any sense. It doesn't make
you more money. Doesn't get you a better
risk to reward. Doesn't better your odds
in winning at all actually. If I can
wait till the horses are out to the
races and see what horse is ahead and I
can then place my bet, it would be a lot
easier to place a bet on whichever horse
is ahead rather than having to place a
bet before any of these horses take off
in the first place. So, this is exactly
that. If I can wait for the market to
show me that it's actually rejecting
this area and going in that direction, I
would much rather wait for that in order
for me to enter this position. So,
that's exactly what I did. I entered the
position after I have the confirmation
that this market is actually headed in
that direction. I placed my stop loss at
an area where if it gets hit, I'm
entirely wrong because if after the
daily time frame we have already had
that wick out, if this daily time frame
comes back up into the upside over here,
that means that we're most likely going
to close above this area of interest,
then we will have a retest of this area
and then head to the upside. Meaning
that I would be entirely wrong about
this position. But since we've had the
liquidity grab, the day after that we
had a rejection and we still closed
below this area of interest, this is
showing me every single possible reason
that it's going to struggle to break
above this area. So, I'm very confident
when it comes to my take profit. [music]
Or I'm sorry, excuse me for my stop
loss. Now, what I did after that was
literally just enter the position. After
I enter the position, what I wait for is
for the market to have FOMC its news
events. And that's exactly what it did.
So, I posted on Instagram that I entered
these positions.
I posted that I was going to wait for
the FOMC to happen at 1:00 p.m. EST.
What ended up happening is that these
news fundamentals actually ended up
happening at 2:00 p.m. EST and they had
this massive push to the downside. The
fundamentals will always follow what the
technicals are doing 80% of the time,
70% of the time. But you just need to
understand how to predict the direction
of the market. So, when I see all of
these indications that this market is
heading to the downside,
and I see this massive news events that
is happening couple of hours before
this trade is setting up the perfect
entry, I'm like, well, the news is
literally going to give it the push that
it needs. I couldn't find any logic as
to why this position should have headed
to the upside. Zero. I could have not
made any sense of it. Now, when you look
at it after the position is gone, it's
like, well, it almost looks quite
obvious. Looks like a very simple break,
>> [music]
>> retest, sell. Break, retest, sell. Very
simple. Now, when it comes to the take
profit placement of this position, I
placed my take profit at the next area
where if it gets hit, my trade can have
a reversal. So, I actually placed my
take profit quite above this area. I
actually ended up placing it somewhere
around here, at a 1:2. I always [music]
have a minimum of a 1:2 risk to reward
in my positions because this way I could
make back my losses whenever I have
losses, which losses are inevitable in
trading. And what happens is after the
market had this massive push to the
downside, I like to follow that momentum
and I ended up closing down here. So, I
never put a take profit because if I am
trading with the trend,
the trend is my friend, I should be
correct about this position for a very
long time. So, I had a 4-hour day trade
entry on this position because I'm
entering off of mainly this daily area
of interest. And I had kind of a daily
take profit. But, if I were to trade
this as a weekly trade and you know, you
guys that can look at this months and
months ahead after this video has been
posted on YouTube, you can come back and
look at this. I believe this market will
be way down here in the future.
Very near future. 4 to 8 weeks this
market could be all the way down here.
Simply because that's just what the
direction of this market is headed to.
That's what this structure is telling
me. I just decided to enter this
position with a day trade and a day take
profit. [music]
And it's what made sense for my position
here. And I was getting out because
obviously at this area whenever we're
above we head up, whenever we're below
we head down. So, if we're above this
area it makes more sense to get out of
it because we can have that reaction to
the upside. So, I always place my take
profit where I can have a reaction from
that area. The closer the better and
always at a minimum of a 1:2. Now,
EUR/USD is pretty much the exact same
thing. I just actually entered off of a
lot of anticipation. This was really a
gamble, I'm not going to lie. And
honestly, this was a bit of high risk
because I technically entered the same
position twice. Now, what do I mean by
that? Well, I entered basically the USD
getting stronger because as you can
tell, EUR/USD sell, strong USD. NZD NZD
USD, sell, strong USD. If the USD would
have gone in the opposite direction, if
it would have gone in weaker, I would
have lost both of these positions. But,
this one was same exact reasoning,
market placement. This market very much
bearish once again. This would be the
lower high on this market right here,
and this would be the lower low on this
market right here. Many would call this
market bearish because of this lower
high and this lower low, and they would
just be wrong. This is the lower high
and this is the lower low. Now, this
market what it has done, it has same
exact thing. Close with a massive
bearish engulfing candlestick, has come
back to retest round psychological level
1.16000,
and it's a very well respected weekly
area. Whenever we're above we'd head up,
whenever we're below we head down,
whenever we're above we head up,
whenever we're below we head down.
Really is that simple. When I go down to
the daily time frame, the daily time
frame has just approached this area,
very well respected as well.
But, the reason why this is a higher
risk trade is because I have no
confirmation. I have no liquidity grab,
I have no rejection candlestick. While
on NZD USD, I have a massive liquidity
grab, I have already a bearish engulfing
candlestick, I have multiple days that
we've been rejecting this area. On EUR
USD, we have none. We have just
approached this area for the first time.
But, once again, since I understand
top-down analysis, when I go down to the
4-hour time frame, I see the 4-hour
creating a 4-hour double top. I look at
my 30-minute shift of structure, I can
see my inverse head and shoulders, I can
see the structure shifting. This is
literally telling me this is not going
to give us any time in order for us to
wait for that confirmation. If we wait
for that daily confirmation, this trade
is going to be gone.
And that's exactly what I did. I decided
to enter this trade without any
confirmation. Now, if I would have lost
this position, I would have been totally
fine with it, because I accept the risk
behind the position, but I would
understand that I entered this position
with no confirmation. There is nothing
on the daily time frame that is telling
me this trade is actually going to the
downside. Zero. Nothing is confirming to
me that we're rejecting this area. So,
this was a bit of higher risk. So, what
I decided to do was have a tighter stop
loss. My stop loss could have definitely
gotten hit, and I would have not been
entirely wrong in this position. This
market could have easily made it up to
the top of this resistance and just
continue selling to the downside exactly
how we did here, exactly how we did
here, exactly how we did throughout all
of this here. So, this trade in general
was just more of a gamble that I decided
to do, and it ended up working out in my
favor once again just because I
understand how the market works and I'm
very in sync with it, but this was
purely, purely, purely, purely based off
of market placement. We're at a strong
support and resistance, small rejection,
take the trade. Nothing else that
indicates to me that it's having strong
rejections. There wasn't an accumulation
how there is here,
and nothing else that can indicate a
Now, my take profit for this trade was a
lot shorter. My take profit was at this
next structure point because that's
where it can have a reaction from, but
what I ended up doing was just following
the momentum. I let the momentum
continue having a push to the downside,
and I ended up closing all the way down
here at the very lows of this 4-hour
candlestick for a 1:4. Now, if I were to
still be holding both of these
positions, this 1:3.69
would be a 1:4.69,
so an extra percent there. And on
NZD/USD, I'd be exactly where I am now.
So, I'd probably be near at that million
dollars. And if I were to continue to
hold probably throughout the duration of
this week and next week, I would
probably hit that goal of a million
dollars. But, since I already decided
that I was more than happy with a 1:2 on
this position, I ended up getting nearly
a 1:4. It was already a high-risk trade
because I had no daily confirmation,
should have been a loss. I still made
profit, Put the wrong tight stop loss,
still made profit. I decided that Oh,
and everything happened so fast, right?
This happened in less than 6 hours. I
decided to not be greedy and not break
my trading plan and overstretch it and
just accept that I have
predicted the direction of this move and
I've capitalized off of it and I move to
the next one. These moves always present
themselves. There's always another
opportunity like this that comes down
the road. I've been at this game long
enough to know that. I've been at this
game long enough to see it that many
times and I just am totally fine if this
market from this moment right here would
just do something like this. I won't
feel any type of way because I already
got what I was okay with and I would
have been not okay if this market came
back and took me out at break even. I've
had every possible scenario happen to me
and this is what I'm very comfortable
with. That's what a lot of traders need
to work on when they enter the trade is
stick to their plan. And this is my
plan. My plan was to put my take profit
at a 1:2 and if it goes past that,
continue with that momentum up until
where it makes sense and then you close
out. And that's exactly how we nearly
made a million dollars in this position.
My million dollar day is coming very
soon and I'm glad that I can have this
momentum happening here at the trading
floor. You guys are probably wondering
where the [__] is Alex. What is he
doing?
Well, this is not my office, right? I I
somewhere very different. I'm building a
trading floor right now. So, this is one
of the desks that is going to be
someone's. Somebody's going to come in
here and use this desk to trade and I've
definitely set the standard quite high.
This is my first time taking a trade
inside of the trading floor and it has
almost been my record breaking trade.
So, whoever's trading at this desk in
the future, good luck. The standards are
very high and I expect nothing other
than what you have just seen in this
video. Full deep understanding of the
exact trade that you're entering.
Knowing why you you be entering it, and
why you shouldn't be entering it and
most importantly accepting the risk. So,
this is a very warm welcoming to the
trading floor. I'm very excited to any
trader that is welcome to come out to
the trading floor. Anybody that wants to
challenge me, I challenge any trader
that would like to sit in one of these
desks over here. Yes, you want to show?
Any desk right here, you guys are
welcome to appear here once you're
invited. This is an invitation only to
be part of this trading floor and out
trade me. If you can out trade me, you
got my respect. If you can't out trade
me,
respectfully, not respectfully, don't
[__] talk about me. You know,
if I got the balls to make $700,000 in 6
hours full porting
at FOMC,
you could have the balls to come in here
and and and and check Bro, Sarah, do you
think they could handle the pressure
sitting right there? You don't think so,
right?
>> of pressure.
>> I don't know if they could, bro.
I'm calling out all traders here on
YouTube as well. Calling out every
single trader. If you think you can out
trade me, I will send out a formal
invitation for you to come out to the
trading floor and out trade me. I will
take my hat off and give you my respects
if you do.
And if you don't, you will be welcome to
leave as well.
And the fact that this was my first
trade here in the trading floor, I feel
myself breaking that seven-figure take
profit happening in this exact same
trading floor with many of you that are
going to be part of this experience. You
guys are my students. You guys are more
than welcome to be invited out here.
We're going to be hosting in-person
events, educating people in person,
training people in person, traders
managing money that I personally will
fund into them. And this is really just
the beginning of the journey. So, if you
guys want to see more about it, hit that
like and subscribe button and
>> you can't stop you.
>> Why? Why?
>> We got to show the trading floor.
>> Oh, we want to
>> What they're waiting
>> Okay, you know what? You're right.
You're right. All right, let's show
them. Let's Let's show them the trading
floor. Let me All right, let's show
them. Let's show them. All right, boys.
This is like weird. We're going from
like sit down video to like a vlog
[laughter] right now.
Let me show you guys a little bit of
what's going on here, right? So, we have
about 12 different spaces that we are
going to be doing here at the trading
floor. So, we're going to have this side
be experienced traders, this side be
unexperienced traders.
>> Really helpful unexperienced
unexperienced trader.
>> Over there that he's already advancing a
little bit. And over here, we're going
to have the edge So, this is going to be
a big glass right here that's going to
separate the traders from one another.
Cameras are already set up. So, you
know, they get into a little bit of
fight, you know, you know who's who
started it.
>> Who won?
>> No, we we we condone that type of stuff,
but like, you know, who who hit who got
the who got the first punch? Who you
know? Educational section over here.
We're going to have a big TV
desk right here so you guys can learn
anybody that comes here in person. We
won't have more than five to eight
people at a time. A similar setup as to
what we have over here. So, this is
going to be the lounge area. So, we're
going to actually have a couch right
here so you can just chill here.
You have a boy Harley cooking up some of
the desk.
So, kitchen's going to be over here.
There's going to be more glass that
separates down here. We're going to
leave space here for one car, which is
going to be
Timing could have not been better for
that.
The Bugatti. Bugatti's going to come
there. Let me show you guys upstairs.
So, up here we just finished the
flooring, which looks very decent, goes
with the vibe. I am not digging these
lights. These lights are a little bit
>> normal.
>> Not too aggressive on on the eyes, you
know, I don't really like it. Yeah, and
it looks too normal. Once Did I give it
a bit more of a vibe? So,
>> They're going to incorporate.
>> Yeah, it's too corporate. We're not
we're not that corporate out here. We're
we're fun. What we do is not corporate,
so why
have corporate lighting? Why have that
being brought down on us? Have you ever
thought about it that way?
The corporate's being being
>> Definitely not what we want.
>> Yeah, we don't want that.
>> We're so We're so not corporate that
we're not even going to put railings.
>> No, we're definitely going to put
railings cuz the other day I was on my
phone and I was like, "Oh!"
>> [laughter]
>> I was literally on my phone and I was
like, "Oh!"
I almost [__] broke my leg.
So, yeah, we actually have railings
coming very soon. Oh, I might put the
Beetle over here.
So,
we might put it over there. I don't know
yet. Might go in the corner.
And we got to check up on that. Oh, we
have to show them the Bugatti if we're
going to do all this now, man. Let's
Let's Let's go show them.
Oh, oh, and by the way, this is just to
show the people
or anybody that is always a curious cat
about the track record. So, right now
the account's sitting at 3.8 million
basically. So, we're up a million
dollars for the month right now.
>> I see a lot of stuff coming in. Not
[__] bad. Not bad.
My Indian [__] friends, what do you
What do you do think?
You think this is good?
Is it really [__] good?
>> [laughter]
>> Oh, man.
Bro, see like come walking out now, bro.
You got to like the
the light difference is just crazy.
Cool transition, right? But you guys
didn't see that one coming.
Boy, Stahli with the creations right
there.
So, this is the Bugatti. This is the
latest update. So, we actually ended up
figuring out that
>> a little different.
>> Oh, this is the wrong purple car. Oh.
The Bugatti.
>> [laughter]
>> They actually look pretty similar, not
going to lie. So,
>> The one has the windshield, the other
one doesn't.
>> We might have to Yeah, but we might have
to end up doing the windshield like
that, bro. Literally like out of the
same material. Did you Did you know?
I just don't know if I trust this going
200 miles an hour.
>> I mean, it's It'll make it more like a
race car.
Wasn't that what we're going for?
>> I don't know if we're going for that
here, man.
But Bugatti's in a very similar state. I
know Matt Armstrong is coming back, I
think, next week and we're going to be
completing the Bugatti, hopefully. So,
we actually got finessed a little bit
with the headlights.
As you guys can see right here, this is
the headlights.
Fully disassembled.
There's more parts of them, I just don't
know where they are.
This is the transmission of
fifth gear of the combobulator that
displays the Gs of the lights.
However that goes.
And yeah, the guys that were supposed to
be repairing them, not
going to talk bad about anybody, but
they [__] us. Took them 2 months to do
nothing essentially. So,
Mr. Matt Armstrong was able to find
headlights somewhere on that side of the
world across the pond, as he would say,
crossing the pond.
And he's going to be bringing some
headlights now, which will be able to
mount onto the body kit that we have for
this car. I don't want to talk about
much what we have for the car in terms
of what is going to happen. All I can
say, this is truly and I mean this from
the bottom of my heart, truly going to
be a one-of-one build. And Bugatti,
you're not ready for what we're about to
do. All I can say
is thank you for not helping us with
this, cuz we're about to have the most
gangster Bugatti Pure Sport in the
[__] world.
>> I don't even think I'm ready.
>> Yeah, I don't even think I'm ready
either, bro.
It's just so dirty right now.
Like
so dusty. It's a shame. We got We We got
to wash it. Where's the key?
Do you know where the key is?
>> I have no idea where the key is.
>> I don't know.
Is she alive? When was the last time we
turned her on?
Ready? When we open the door, the fuel
pump
3 2 1
>> Start.
>> Bro, she just wants to live.
Where is the key though?
Oh, it's right there. I see the key
right there.
No, girl, don't worry. Trust, believe
me. When you're back on the road,
I will not hold back. We got a lot of
lost time that you need to make up
and we will
hit top speed again.
Believe me.
Thank you guys very much for like
watching this video to the end. Hit that
like and subscribe button.
>> You have a whole gym.
>> Bro, [__] And dude, I have so much
[__] bro.
Bro, I was stressed out.
Shout out to Adin Ross. Adin Ross, he
was getting rid of his gym, literally
getting ready to toss it out into the
garbage. I'm like, "Wait. Wait. Wait. I
need a gym."
So, Adin hooked it up with his entire
gym setup. It's a bit messy right now,
but we have dumbbells all the way up to
hundreds. Literally everything that you
would need for a full gym setup. We will
be having a calisthenic area in here
because I'm a pretty calisthenic person
myself. You know, I can like
do pull-ups and [__] Can you do
pull-ups?
Of course I can do pull-ups. Can't do
more than me, though.
>> Can't do muscle-ups.
>> You can't?
>> No.
>> Oh, that's easy, bro.
Some fans, some haters haven't learned
yet.
How many you want, bro?
>> Three.
>> Ah.
>> [sighs]
>> FBI yeah, come back. Come here.
It's the mic, guys, for the video.
But, we got the gym
and uh a lot more things that we will be
updating as we develop more of the
compound that we have coming on. All I
got to say, hit that like and subscribe
button. See you boys in the next one and
set and [__] forget.